hakshop.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy - Hak5

As hackers, we hold your privacy with the highest respect. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared – and we know you're smarter than the average bear when it comes to this. The below describes what information we collect from our website users and it's used. By visiting one of our listed websites, you are accepting the practices described within. Hak5.org Hakshop.com, WiFiPineapple.com, USBRubberDucky.com, LANTurtle.com, BashBunny.com, PacketSquirrel.com

We're morally against violating your right to privacy, or annoy you for that matter. To that end we’ve made it easy to opt out of our newsletter and opt out of having your data collected when you visit our site.

##    
ORDER FULFILLMENT INFORMATION

When you purchase products through our website, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, phone number and email address. All of these pieces of information are necessary to ship your order. We do not share any of your contact information with anybody other than our third party order fulfillment vendors and fraud protection services. We retain your shipping details and order history to enable us to provide you with future customer services like returns and warranty replacements. If you create a hakshop.com account we store your account password, which you can reset or change at any time. Your password is only accessible by you and never by Peak Design employees or third parties.

## CREDIT CARD PROCESSING

Hak5 does not collect or store credit card information provided when making a purchase on our website. All credit card transactions are handled by our third party payment gateways and merchant services.

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

## WEBSITE ANALYTICS

We use Google Analytics to track the volume and type of traffic that comes to our website. When you access this website Google may collect information such as cookies, IP address, search keywords, session length, browser type, page views and number of visits. None of this information is personally identifiable, and is subject to Google’s Privacy Policy. You have the option to opt out of our Google Analytics by opting out in your [Ads Control Panel](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or in the global [ad network privacy](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). You can also install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) in your browser.

## DIGITAL MARKETING & RETARGETING

We use a few different digital marketing services to create and display online ads for our products. As you browse hakshop.com, these services use cookies to remember what products you viewed and clicked on. Our advertising partners then enable us us to present you with advertising based on your previous interaction with hakshop.com. You might see Peak Design ads on other websites, on Facebook and Instagram, or while watching videos on Youtube or other platforms. This practice is called “retargeting.” We don’t collect any personally identifiable information about you (like name or email) until you make a purchase. We also don’t directly retain your digital marketing information—instead, that data is retained by our third party marketing services.

You can also opt out of retargeting service by visiting the following links. Please note that these platforms allow you to opt out of interest-based advertising delivered by registered members on the current browser you are using.

For US:

For EU:

## CUSTOMER SUPPORT

We use a third party service to host and manage our Support Center and Contact Us form. When you fill out the Contact Us form or email shop@hak5.org, our support service retains all of the information you provided, including your name and email. This information enables our support team to see a history of your support inquiries and provide you with the best possible service. Your customer service history is only accessible by the Hak5 Customer Service team.

## NEWSLETTER

If you sign up or opt in to the Hak5 Newsletter we will collect your name and email address for the purposes of sending you occasional updates about our company. We will never share or sell this information to anybody without your consent, and you can unsubscribe at any time.

Google Analytics is Google’s web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how their visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics collects information anonymously, and much like examining footprints in sand, it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Analytics uses its own cookie to track visitor interactions. The cookie is used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve their website and how people find it. A different cookie is used for each website, and visitors are not tracked across multiple sites. Analytics requires that all websites that use it must update their privacy policy to include a notice that fully discloses the use of Analytics. To disable this type of cookie, some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis. In addition to declining cookies, you can also install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)in your browser, which prevents Google Analytics from collecting information about your website visits.

Hak5 takes security seriously and cares about the integrity of your personal information. We use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological methods to transmit and store your data in a secure, encrypted manner. However, Hak5 cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat our security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

No, we don’t. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or via our social media channels. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.  
PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline or through other platforms or channels

Please also visit our Legal Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

By using our site, you consent to this web site privacy policy.

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

This policy was last modified on 5/24/2018

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at shop@hak5.org
